Let's go with the AT accept.py, so this is one of our best methods to bypass EDR sometime.
So basically, in the previous video, the SMB-Exacan PSX was creating a noisy services that
can be easily detected by EDR, so there is new service here created, and it's too suspicious.
The EDR will easily catch those services, and it will alert the analyst who is working.
So instead of using the PSX can SMB-Exacan, you can use AT-Exacan to evade, to hide from these
EDRs.
It makes your tactics more still there than creating a new service, okay?
Only AT accept leverages task scheduler service on the windows, and it will use the SMB server
message block to authenticate, and use task scheduler remote procedure call to temporarily
create a task.
So it will create a task temporarily, and it will delete the task once the task has been
completed, okay?
So it uses, once again, it uses a SMB for an authentication, so once it gets authenticated,
it will use task scheduler remote procedure call, or PC, to create a temporary task, like
who am I?
We are giving you who am I, it's a temporary task, and it will execute the task once the task
has been completed, it will remove the task, okay?
So I will execute this command, who am I, and now you can see creating a task, it created
a temporary task, and it ran the task, so here is the result of the task, and it deleted
the task, right?
So creating, running, deleting, so this will be best, best, and best thing, so coming
up to the security, the defense mechanism tool, so if I give the AR, so it created
a task, and it gives a result, and terminated, and close the connection, right?
So the investigation part, if you go to the security log, you can find out there is a log
on type 3, because we are using the SMB for authenticate, the network log on protocol,
so here you can find a few information, so here you can see, it was giving the IP address
with the target state, and the user is an user, he executed, he just log into network-based
log-ons, like SMB, and we don't know what he executed, but we just got a log-on information
side, so this looks like the normal, so the EDRs and analysts who doesn't know what happened
in the machine, so until and unless there's a process activity or running process of the
port, okay?
So the commands are pretty easy, so we are going to complete the impact, we have a few
more impact-based commands, if you need, you can use that also, but three are very familiar
in a hackers perspective, so I have took this three, and created a video, let's hop
of them here and we will connect you guys in the next video. See you. Bye bye.